

BASTIAN **DAMMANN**

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I am an ambitious and driven individual who has recently gained valuable experience in a one-year full stack development training. I am now seeking opportunities with forward-thinking organizations that undertake agile projects. My primary expertise lies in JavaScript, particularly with React and Express frameworks. However, I am also enthusiastic about expanding my programming language repertoire and prove my adaptability, logical thinking and strong receptiveness by acquiring additional certifications that enhance my personal and company's value.

1

+49 176 444 800 42



dammann.bastian@gmail.com

Javascript

Deact

Node Express

Git

Frameworks:

Version Control:



Johanna-Dachs-Str. 56 93055 Regensburg



<u>LinkedIn Profile</u>



Portfolio

SKILLS

Technologies:

- JavascriptHTML5
- CSS/SASS
- _ .

Database:

- Lowdb
- MongoDB

Other: Agile Development

- Project Management
- Teamplayer
- Logical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- German (mother tongue)
- English (B2)
- French, Spanish (A1)

RELEVANT PROJECTS

- Development of a React web application utilizing an API to construct a comprehensive Blizzard Hearthstone card browser with multiple complex filtering mechanisms (<u>Github Repo</u>)
- Flawless project management for the renovation of an occupied residential building, showcasing exceptional communication, problem-solving skills and empathy (<u>Housing</u> association)
- Project planning of a showroom in an Al startup for demonstrating their software to potential clients - proving UX/UI-design thinking, creativity and cost management skills (Showroom Demo)

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT

DCI Digital Career Institute GmbH, Berlin

10/2022 - Present

- Programming bootcamp for frontend development
- Strong knowledge in HTML, CSS/SASS, Javascript/React
- Advanced knowledge about backend engineering with node.js, express.js, MongoDB

B. SC. IBA - RENEWABLE ENERGIES (Ø 1.9)

SRH University, Berlin

04/2014 - 09/2018

• IBA with focus on renewable energie technologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

O ENGINEER FOR TECHNICAL BUILDING EQUIPMENT JOHANN BUNTE SE & Co. KG / BWE Ing. GmbH, Berlin/Ragow

03/2019 - 12/2021

- Permanent position as specialist planner for building technology (heating/electrical systems, elevators)
- Independent project management for renovations of residential buildings without complaints of the tenants
- Project work on the construction of schools, kindergartens and office buildings with loads of regulations and standards that require an eye for the details

INTERNSHIP AS PROJECT PLANNER

ifesca GmbH, Illmenau

08/2017 - 10/2017

- Project planning for a showroom where the developed software is presented to potential customers
- The concept I designed was used for the construction of the showroom (see ifesca.de)
- Working in an agile environment (scrum) together with Al engineers and frontend developers